Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh City Council, 1963-2010; 1987-2002; I.
  - Alphabetical Subject Files, 1976-2003; 1987-2001; 1.
    - Hotel Room Occupancy Tax, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Housing- General, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Housing Court Continuance, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Housing Market in Pittsburgh, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - How to Become a Democratic Committee Person, 1976-1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Hunger Services Trust Fund, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Hydroelectric Plant, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Immaculate Heart of Mary Lot, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - I-Net Files, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Industrial Policy, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Institute of Politics, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Intergovernmental Cooperation, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Intermunicipal Liquor Licenses Transfers, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Investment- "South Africa", 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Iron City Beer, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Italian Sister City, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Jackson Street, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Jackson Street Blockwatch, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - J.K.'s Bar, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Jancy Street Blockwatch, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Jobs, circa 1993 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Jobs in Pittsburgh, 1981-1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Joe Kelly, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Joe Natoli Field, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Julco Enterprises, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Katz, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Keystone Lumber, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Kids Around Town, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - KidWatch, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Kincaid Street Basketball Court, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Kings Estate, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Kingsley Association, 1990-2002 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Kiosk, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Kohn, Joseph, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Kolenda Night Song Sheet, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Korean War Veterans, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kosmos, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Krystopolski, Harriet, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Lamar Issues, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Landmark America, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Landmark Inc., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Larimer Basketball Court, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Lawful Conduct of Bingo, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lawrenceville Drug Rally, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Lead Dust, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Lead Poisoning, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - League of Women Voters of the Pittsburgh Area, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - LaMont, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Lesbian Studies, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Leslie Park, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Liberty Avenue Liquor Sign, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Liberty Donofrio (3947-49), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Liberty Park Resident Council, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Lighting, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Light of Life, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Liller File, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Linoleum Way, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Liquor Control Board, 1992-2002 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Liquor Licenses, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Liquor Transfer, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Litter, 1989-2002 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Local 57, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Local Economy, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Loitering, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Lower Chartiers Watershed Council, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Macroburst, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Magistrate Court, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Maglev, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Maglev, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Magnetic Levitation, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Mahon Street, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Managed Care Workers' Comp. Program, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Map Pittsburgh, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Marina, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Marina Project, 1982-1990 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Mariott Courtyard at Liberty and Baum, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Martinez, Gil, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. Commission, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Maumax Building, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Mayor's Service Center, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Mayoral Succession, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Mazeroski Field, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - McCandless/ Leslie Playgrounds, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - McGann, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Meals on Wheels, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Medicare Overcharge Measure, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mellon Park Air Dome, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Mellon Street, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Mellon Street Market, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Mellon Street Revitalization, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Memorial Day Program, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Memorials and Statues, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Mental Health Programs, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Merlot Tarpulin Company, circa 1980 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Metal Detectors, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Metropolitan Pittsburgh Crusade for Voters, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Metropolitan Tenants Organization, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Military Spending, 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Millvale Property Dispute, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Minority/Women Business Enterprise, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Minority Set-Asides, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Minority Women Shelter Programs, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Requests, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Mobile Patrol, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Modena, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Mon/Ohio Development and Reconstruction, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Mon Valley Express, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Moore Park- Brookline Landfill/Soccer Field, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Mossfield EMS, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Morrow Park, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Mount Washington "Grandview", 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Movies in the Park, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Mr. John Rental Portable Chemical Toliets, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Municipal Finance, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Municipal Law, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Municipal Parking Tax Pension, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Murphy, Tom, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Murphy's Millions, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Murray Hill Avenue Historic District Nomination, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Murray Hill Designation, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - M/WBE Contract Review Summary, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - M/WBE Performance Audit, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - M/WBE Plan Review Summary, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - M/WBE Plan Review Summary, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - NAACP Scip Center, 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Nabisco, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - National Healthcare Debate, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - National Indoor Tennis, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - National Industry Heritage, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - NBDR Program, 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Neighborhoods 2000- Citizens' Budget Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Neighborhoods 2000- CBC Focus Groups, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Neighborhoods 2000- CBC Participant Sign In Sheets, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Neighborhood Assistance Program, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Neighborhood Block Watch, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Neighborhood Employment Center (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Neighborhood Employment Project, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Neighborfare Board of Directors, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Neighborline, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Neighborhood Link, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Neighborhood Safety Program, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Negley Corridor, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Negley North, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Nelson Mandela Peace Park Garfield, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Newsclippings, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings (Jim Ferlo), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo), 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo) January-March, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo) April to June, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo) July to September, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo) October to December, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Newsclippings (Ferlo), 1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Vending Law, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Nicaragua, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Nine Mile Run, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Ninth Ward Youth Association, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Noise, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Noise Ordinance, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Noncomforming Use/Rezoning Procedure, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Non-Profits Game of Chance, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - North Shore Connector Impact Statement, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - No Trash Initiative, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Nuclear Holocaust, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Nuisance Bars, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Nuisance Properties, circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Oakland Bus Lane, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Occupational Health, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - OMB Watch, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - OMI, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Operation Clean Sweep, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Originals, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Orioles- Cuban National Team, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - PAGIS, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Paint Specifications, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Pall Corporation- Microfiltration, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Pamphlets, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Panhandling, circa 1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Panther Hollow Project, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Panther Hollow TIF, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Paper Street, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Paramedics, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Parity Laws, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Parking Authority, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Parking Authority Giveaway, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Parking- Holiday, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Parking Issues, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Parking Lots, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Parking Lot Legislation, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Parking Meter Legislation, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Parking Pads, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Parking Permit, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Parking Tax Increase, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Parks Conservancy, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Parks Master Planning, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Park Rangers, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Parkway Center Development, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Parternship for Medical Renaissance, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Pasquarelli, 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Pay Equity (Literature and Research), 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Pay Equity Coalition of Southwest Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Pay Equity Sample Legislation, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Pay Phone, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - PBS, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Peabody Writing Workshop, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Peace Park, 1995-2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Penn Avenue Temp Improvement, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Penn Circle, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - PennDot Handicap Ramps, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Penn Liberty Association, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Penn and Liberty Projects, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Economy League, 1993-2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Fair Tax Coalition, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Housing Finance Agency, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania Pension Fund, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania Southwest, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Water Company, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - People's Natural Gas Company Case, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Permits, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Permit Parking at the Stadiums, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Persad Center, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Personal Care Homes, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - PCC Car, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Pharmacy, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Phipps, 1993-1999 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Pikkas (John) Parking Lot, 610 Third Ave, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Pittsburgh Advisory Committee on Housing Community Development, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Pittsburgh AIDS Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh Building and Construction Trades Council, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Pittsburgh Business Resource Center, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group-Budget Positions, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Community Reinvestment Group- Proclamations, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Community Services, Inc., 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust- Arts Service Committee, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust- Meeting, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust- Board of Trustees, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Development Fund, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Development Fund- Business Development Center Program Summary, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Partnership, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Facts, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Film Office, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Firefighters Local #1, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Folk Music Society, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Founders Council, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Glass Center, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Heritage, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Housing Development Corporation, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh Labor Action Network for the Americas, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Pittsburgh Literacy Initiative, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Pittsburgh Marathon, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Pittsburgh Mediation Center, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh Mural, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Pittsburgh Outdoor Advertising, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Pittsburgh Pirates Baseball Club, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Pittsburgh Poor, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Pittsburgh Promotion, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Pittsburgh Property Assessment Gentrification, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Pittsburgh Recycles, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Pittsburgh Recycles, 1987-1991 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh Recycles, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh's Regional Master Plan, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Pittsburgh Rugby Club, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Pittsburgh Sports and Festival Federation, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - The Pittsburgh Symphony Society, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Pittsburgh Urban Magnet Project, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Pittsburgh Water and Sewer Authority, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Pittsburgh Water and Sewer Authority, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Pittsburgh Works, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Pittsburgh Zoo, 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Plan B, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Planning Commission, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Plant Closing Notification, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Plastic Pipe, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
    - Player Tax, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Playground Construction, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Playground Safety, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Point State Park, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Police Complaints, 1992-1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Police Disciplenary Review, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Police Hiring, 1989-1994 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Police Misconduct, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Police Pension Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Police- Swimming Pools, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Police Video Surveillance, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Polygraphs, circa 1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Pool Fees, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Pools, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Port Authority, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Ports of Pittsburgh Commission, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Postage, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Post Office Parking Lot, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - POW/MIA Flag, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Predatory Lending, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Proc Stuff, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Preemptions, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Preservation Awards, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Articles of Interest/Other Information, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Bylaws in Progress, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh Correpsondence/Relations with Other Organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Interim Planning Overlay District, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Irene, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh Miscellaneous, 1991-1997 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Money, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh- Outreach, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh Stationary, undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh Subcommittee, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Presley Street High Rise, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Press Releases, 1988-1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Pressure Chemical, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Prevailing Wages, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Private Communication Systems, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Private Industry Council, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Private Mintwood Street, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Private Right of Action, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Privitization, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Procurement Policy, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Produce Terminal, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Project 21, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Project Vote, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Property Assessment, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Property Maintenance Program, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Property Tax Assessment, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Psychic/Silent Witness, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Public Art in Pittsburgh, circa 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Public Drunks, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Public Hearings-Rules of Council, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Public Housing Youth, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Public Official Standing, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Public Owned Property, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Public Safety Building Regulations, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Public Safety Complex, 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Public Safety Study, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Public Works Park Zones (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Racial Relations, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Rainbow Coalition, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Rainforest, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - RAIUSA, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Reapportionment, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Recycling, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Recycling Awareness Day, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Recycling Plan Bill #1087, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Redeemer Church, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Refrigerators, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Regatta Issues, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Regional Asset District, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Regional Industrial Development Corporation, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Regional Parks, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Regional Revenue Sharing, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Rehabilitation Institute, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Religious Round Table, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Rental Agreement Information, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Reservoir, 1994-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Residency Requirements, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Residency FOP, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Residential LERTA Program, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Residential TIF, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Residential Parking Permit Program, 1993-2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Retiree Health Benefits, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Retiree Life Insurance, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Retirement Programs, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Rezzetano Properties, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Rezoning McMonagle, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Rice, Scott, 1979-1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - 5329 Rippey St Demoliton, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - River Avenue Project Relocation of Tenants, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Riverboat Gambling, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Riverboat Safety, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Riverfront Rezoning, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Rheumatoid Society, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Riverfronts, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Riverfront Park, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - River Rescue Site, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - River Task Force, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Roadster Cafe, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Roaring Run Watershed Association, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Robert, Crawford, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Robeson, Paul- Tribute, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Robotics Institute- Lawrenceville, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Rodeo, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Rodeo- Animal Rights, 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Rodeo Legislation, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Rooftop and Billboard Signs, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Rooming Houses, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Rottweilers, 938 North Highland, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Route 51, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Rubinoff Company Development, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Rx Council Of Western Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Sadowski Marker, circa 1995 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Safe Kids, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - St. Clair (N 706), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - St. Clair (N. Zoning), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - St. Clair Village Postive Attitudes in Public Housing Communities, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - St. Francis, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - St. Joe's Nursing Center, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - St. Mary's Art Program, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - St. Mary's Priory, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - St. Nicholas, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - St. Raphael's After School, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Salak, Eleanor, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Saltzburg Demonstration (Shipments of CS Gas from Federal Labs), 1990 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Salvation Army PHCA, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Sargent Electric, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Schenley Center, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Schenley Golf Course, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 32)